Harold Stein Filk Collection
Harold Stein Filk Archive
- Ephemera
  - Postcards
    Intended for unused postcards not better categorized elsewhere.
    - Personal card from Chris Conway, Conway, Chris; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Convention: NA; genreform: Postcard (Box 7)
    - MASSFILC logo postcard, 2012; NEFilk 22. Concertino 2012; 1 copy; Notes: Vampire note on staff logo "A Sharp Note" by Virginia Taylor Convention: NEFilk 22: ConCertino 2012; genreform: Postcard (Box 8)
      Convention -- NEFilk 22. ConCertino 2012; Postcard
    - NEFilk logo postcard, 2012; NEFilk 22. Concertino 2012; 1 copy; Notes: NEFilk Logo by Matt Leger Convention: NEFilk 22: ConCertino 2012; genreform: Postcard (Box 8)
    - Promotional postcard for Portal Through the Pond, David K. Anderson, 2 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Postcard (Box 9)
      Postcard; ephemera
    - Postcard to Lisa Wahl advertising Serious Steel, 1999; Random Factors; 1 copy; Notes: Torrance, CA cancel code Origin: Random Factors, 1999; genreform: Postcard (Box 10)
    - Kip Rosser, Music and Performance on the thermain (postcard), Rosser, Kip; 1 copy; Notes: Promotional postcard Origin: Convention: NA; genreform: Postcard (Box 7)
    - postcard from the Kickstarter campaign for PDX Broadsides' fourth album Trust Issues, PDX Broadsides; 1 copy; Notes: This is a color postcard from the Kickstarter campaign for PDX Broadsides' fourth album Trust Issues Origin: PDX Broadsides; genreform: Postcard from the PDX Broadsides (Box 2)
    - Art by I Abra Cinii from Concertino 2012 (postcard), 1 copy; Notes: Title of the artwork is Shalan Pana Origin:; genreform: Postcard (Box 8)
    - Bad Idea #1227 - The H.M.S. Bad idea (postcard), 1 copy; Notes: It's possible Harold had this because H.M.S. were his initials. Origin:; genreform: Postcard (Box 7)
    - Collector Post Card #3 of 10, The Andrew Allen Trio; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: CD campaign Convention: NA; genreform: Postcard (Box 7)
    - Looney Labs Pyramid promo postcard, 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Convention: NA; genreform: Postcard (Box 7)
  - Stickers
    - Egyptian deities with guitars and drums on a bumper sticker, 1 copy; Notes: Commercial bumper sticker Origin: Possibly bought for/from Interfilk Convention: NA; genreform: Bumper Sticker (Box 7)
      Convention -- NA; Bumper Sticker; ephemera
    - Badger in a bag sticker, 1 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Sticker (Box 7)
      Sticker; ephemera
    - Wizard Moon sticker, 1 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Sticker (Box 7)
  - 3 different art prints from the Alligator Stretch Goal level in Bestey Tinney's kickstarter for Release the Cello, Tinney, Betsey; 3 copy; Notes: Origin: Betsey Tinney Convention: NA; genreform: Art Prints (Box 9)
    Convention -- NA; Art Prints; ephemera
  - 99 Songs by Efen Wealt, Wealt, Efan; 1 copy; Notes: A list of songs with how long they are and what album they appear on. Origin: Convention: NA; genreform: List (Box 7)
    Convention -- NA; List; ephemera
  - A list of NE Filkers, 1 copy; Notes: From a very narrow time frame, as it includes both Badger and Rob Balder. Annotations about both Lunacon and Philcon circa 2009 Origin: NA Convention: NA; genreform: List of filkers (Box 7)
    Convention -- NA; List of filkers; ephemera
  - Acoustic World Music, Oplanad, Tania; Freeman, Mike; 1 copy; Notes: www.opland-freeman.com Origin: NA; genreform: Flier (Box 2)
  - Ad for Midlife Crisis, 18 October 1982; Robinson, James, Dr.; McQuillin, Cynthia, 1953-2006; 1 copy; Notes: Pink, one sided (James listed as Jane) Origin: 30242; genreform: Leaflet (Box 2)
    Leaflet; ephemera
  - Ad for Rounds Galore a book of rounds from Sol Weber, Weber, Sol; 1 copy; Notes: White one-sheet with photographs, very crumpled Origin: Weber, Sol; genreform: One sheet (Box 2)
    One sheet; ephemera
  - Anatomy of a Filk, Cinii, Ariel; 1 copy; Notes: Has songs in it: Song are Right and Left Grand by Cat Faber, The Wolf Within by Mark Mandel, Take My Name by I Abra Cinii, four sheets double sided Origin:; genreform: Article (Box 7)
    Article; ephemera
  - Back to the Future the Card Game - Promotional Card, Looney Labs; 1 copy; Notes: 1 card for a Pizza Rehydrator (bonus card to add to deck) Origin:; genreform: Game piece (Box 9)
    Game piece; ephemera
  - Blank volunteer hours sheet, 1 copy; Notes: Origin: undated; genreform: Volunteer Sheet (Box 9)
    Volunteer Sheet; ephemera
  - Borken Telephone, Rock, Paper, Cynic; 3 copy; Notes: Three cards from a collectible card game to promote the album Borken Telephone (the phone is borked) Origin:; genreform: Game cards (Box 7)
    Game cards; ephemera
  - Borken Telephone, Rock, Paper, Cynic; 1 copy; Notes: This is the album the card game is advertising. The data stick is signed. Origin: Convention: NA; genreform: USB stick (Box 7)
    Convention -- NA; USB stick; ephemera
  - Canticles kickstater fliers (glossy), Adams, Alexander James; 3 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Flier (Box 9)
  - Captain Marvel Culture.com, Lequidre, Zorikh; Azriliant, Evan; 1 copy; Notes: Half page of a promotoin for a book and video project being promoted by a filker Origin: Zorikh; genreform: Pamphlet (Box 2)
    Pamphlet; ephemera
  - CD Woodbury Band, 1 copy; Notes: Origin: CD Woodbury Convention: NA; genreform: Commercial DVD (Box 5)
    Convention -- NA; Commercial DVD; ephemera
  - Cesi n'est pas un ribon, 1 copy; Notes: Fannish ribbon for wearing on your con badge. Origin: Convention: NA; genreform: Ribbon (Box 7)
    Convention -- NA; Ribbon; ephemera
  - Cheshire Moon, 1 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Sticker (Box 7)
  - Chicon Doily Cart Player Present Choice of Endings, 1 September 2012; 1 copy; Notes: Musical by Brenda Sutton based on the Mrs. Ruth stories by Tanya Huff Origin: 41153 Convention: NA; genreform: Card (Box 7)
  - Christmas card from Jeri Adkins, 2014; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Personal correspondance from 2014 Convention: NA; genreform: Card (Box 7)
  - Cookie monster card from Vanessa Cardui, Cardui, Vanessa; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Personal correspondance Convention: NA; genreform: Card (Box 7)
  - Cover of Songs of Legends to Come w/ Iron and Steel sheet music on the back, 1979; Wayne, Phillip; 1 copy; Notes: White, double sided Origin: 1979; genreform: Leaflet (Box 2)
  - Dancing With the Fay (with a dancing fairy), 1 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Sticker (Box 7)
  - Dark Deeds & Desperate Men (and Women), Rogow, Roberta; Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios; genreform: CD insert (Box 1)
    CD insert card; ephemera
  - Download code for SJ Tucker in the form of a sticker, 1 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Sticker (Box 7)
  - Dr. Who Drinking Game, 1 copy; Notes: Double sided printout, Tom Baker era (?) Origin: (from Unknown Origin) is printed on the sheet; genreform: Game (Box 10)
    Game; ephemera
  - Erwin S. (Filthy Pierre) Strauss' O*F*F*I*C*I*A*L CAMP LUNACON SINGALONG, Strauss, Erwin S.; 1 copy; Notes: A one-sheet listing songs to be sung at a programming item at a Lunacon. Origin: Distributed by Filthy Pierre at a Lunacon (year unknown); genreform: One sheet (Box 2)
  - Everafter, 2006; 1 copy; Notes: Sewn with a ribbon, picture on cover of Heather Alexander aka Alexander James Adams, collector's edition, #11 Origin: Sea Fire Productions; genreform: Chapbook (Box 16)
    Chapbook; ephemera
  - Filkers of the Night, 1 copy; Notes: Fannish ribbon for wearing on your con badge. Origin: Convention: NA; genreform: Ribbon (Box 7)
  - Final Ballot Pegasus Awards 2016, 1 copy; Notes: blank ballot Origin:; genreform: Ballot (Box 9)
    Ballot; ephemera
  - Flier for debut album for gas and vinyl by SROS LORDS.com, SROS LORDS; 1 copy; Notes: Neon green flier Origin: Convention: NA; genreform: Flier (Box 7)
    Convention -- NA; Flier; ephemera
  - Flier for Xenofilkia, 1 copy; Notes: White flier, dates at least 20 years after the first publication, but no date is given Origin:; genreform: Flier (Box 15)
  - Folk Music in a Digital Age - download sheet, Childs-Helton, Sally; 1 copy; Notes: Yellow paper half-sheet, abstract of Sally Childs-Helton's famous Folk Music in a Digital Age article Origin: Childs-Helton, Sally; genreform: Ad (Box 9)
    Ad; ephemera
  - For a shirt, 2 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Buttons (Box 7)
    Buttons; ephemera
  - Generic black kippah, Harold Stein; 1 copy; Notes: It's black, it's polyester Origin: Harold Convention: NA; genreform: Black kippah (Box 7)
    Convention -- NA; Black kippah; ephemera
  - Getting Started with the Mountain Dulcimer, 1 October 2008; 1 copy; Notes: Picture of Peter playing dulcimer on the front cover. Spiral bound Origin:; genreform: Instructions (Box 16)
    Instructions; ephemera
  - Google Groups thread with lyrics of Spaceship Yourself by Terence Chua, 2004; 1 copy; Notes: Three single-sided sheets, unbound Origin:; genreform: Printout (Box 16)
    Printout; ephemera
  - Gophering benefits, 1 copy; Notes: Has Harold's mailing address written on the back in marker Origin: DucKon, unknown year; genreform: Convention Documents (Box 15)
    Convention Documents; ephemera
  - Has names of filkers written on it and the word Reserved, 1 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Scrap paper (Box 7)
    Scrap paper; ephemera
  - Heather Dale promotional cards, Dale, Heather; 2 copy; Notes: Perpetual Gift album download card Origin: Convention: NA; genreform: Card (Box 7)
  - How to make a coffee can bow, 1 August 1989; 1 copy; Notes: Instructions with illustrations Origin:; genreform: Instructions (Box 16)
  - How to Print on a CD, 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Convention: NA; genreform: Instructions (Box 7)
    Convention -- NA; Instructions; ephemera
  - I'm a Dreamer from PaganBran.com, 1 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Sticker (Box 7)
  - Itinerary for Harold, 1 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Itinerary (Box 9)
    Itinerary; ephemera
  - John Hall bear@di.org - copy of Bob Asprin tape from Chambanacon, 1 copy; Notes: Need to check on status with John Hall Origin: Convention: NA; genreform: Tag (Box 7)
    Convention -- NA; Tag; ephemera
  - Lianin Sidhe (possibly from her Kickstarter), 1 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Thank you note (Box 9)
    Thank you note; ephemera
  - List of contents for Recycled Rogow, Rogow, Roberta; Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Notes: Personal communication Origin: Roberta Rogow/Floating Filk Studios Convention: NA; genreform: List of contents (Box 7)
    Convention -- NA; List of contents; ephemera
  - Locus, March 2008, 1 copy; Notes: Charlie Stross on the cover Origin:; genreform: Magazine (Box 8)
    Magazine; ephemera
  - Loose production papers for various CDs Harold produced for NEFilk year CDs, and CDs for Roberta Rogow, 1 copy; Notes: Copies of the actual CDs and j-cards are available elsewhere in the archive. 9 sheets Origin:; genreform: Printout (Box 14)
  - Map of Setac, 1 copy; Notes: Map of Setac area, possibly from a Conflikt or a Seattle worldcon? Origin: NA; genreform: Map (Box 2)
    Map; ephemera
  - Media Guest biography, 1 copy; Notes: Single sided. Looks like it was inserted at the last minute. They seem to have omitted him from the program book. Origin:; genreform: Handout (Box 14)
    Handout; ephemera
  - Membership form for Boskone 52, 1 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Flier (Box 9)
  - Musical note coaster with piano keys, 1 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Coaster (Box 8)
    Coaster; ephemera
  - NorthAmeriCon 17, 2017; 2 copy; Notes: Glossy flier Origin: July 6-9, 2017; genreform: Flier (Box 9)
  - Original advertising poster for Sourcery by Terry Pratchett - possibly from Science Fiction Mysteries and More, Kirby; 1 copy; Notes: Poster for Terry Pratchett's Sourcery with insert posters for The Light Fantastic, The Colour of Magic, Equal Rites and Mort Origin: ?; genreform: Poster (Box 2)
    Poster; ephemera
  - Paths Through the Babylon Wood, 2009; McGuire, Seanan; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: 2009 limited edition poetry chapbook; genreform: Chapbook (Box 7)
  - PDX Broadsides - Accoustic Kitty is listening, 1 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Sticker (Box 7)
  - PDX Broadsides - Octopus sticker, 1 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Sticker (Box 7)
  - PDX Broadsides - We're the Revolution (someone waving a staff), 1 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Sticker (Box 7)
  - Pegasus Awards 2014 Final Ballot, 1 copy; Notes: Tucked inside Archon 39 songbook Origin:; genreform: Ballot (Box 9)
  - Pegasus Awards 2016 Brainstorming - mail-in, 1 copy; Notes: Brainstorming ballot 2016 Origin:; genreform: Brainstorming Poll (Box 9)
    Brainstorming Poll; ephemera
  - Pegasus Final Ballot, 2015, OVFF 31 (2015); 1 copy; Notes: Origin: OVFF 2015; genreform: Ballot (Box 9)
  - Procrastinators of the Apocalypse Bonus CD, Cirque du So What?; 2 copy; Notes: Origin: Visit us online at www.CirqueDuSowhat.net or if you can't spell that, go to www.baconnipples.com @2010 FIDIM Interactive, LLC. Convention: NA; genreform: Supporting materials (Box 2)
    Convention -- NA; Supporting materials; ephemera
  - Promotion flier for Talis Kimberley's Scarlet for Hunting, 2000; 1 copy; Notes: Red printing, greyscale photo on CD jcard Origin: Marchwood Media; genreform: Flier (Box 14)
  - Promotion flier for Third Thyme's the Charm for $15, 2012; 1 copy; Notes: Color flier with release date June 1, 2012 Origin: Bedlam House; genreform: Flier (Box 14)
  - Publicity photo from Snow White - The Mirror's Revenge, 1 copy; Notes: Photo features Kristoph Klover and Margaret Davis with Jerry Hartlove (?) and Jeslyn Kati (?) Origin:; genreform: Publicity Photo (Box 8)
    Publicity Photo; ephemera
  - Random Factors invoices for CDs and songbooks, 1996; Random Factors; 2 copy; Notes: From 1996 Origin: Random Factors, 1996; genreform: Invoice (Box 10)
    Invoice; ephemera
  - Reimbursement for CDs for creating con CD for Contertino 2018, 1 copy; Notes: On MASSFILC letterhead, unsigned Origin:; genreform: Letter (Box 8)
  - Rune-themed greeting cards, probably from the Sundown kickstarter, Sassafras; 4 copy; Notes: Different runes on each card Origin: Probably Sassafrass Convention: NA; genreform: Greeting cards (Box 7)
  - Saturday Open Mic 2x10 Sign-Ups, 1 copy; Notes: Handwritten sheet. Particpants include Judy Kay Craft, Steve Swope, David Kushner, Kris Wildman, BLC, Jamie Peters, Kit Peters, David Wilford Origin: Unknown; genreform: Sign Up Sheet (Box 9)
    Sign up sheet; ephemera
  - Science Fiction Song Sheet, 1 copy; Notes: Double sided Origin:; genreform: Handout (Box 14)
  - Solar Sailors, The Dehorn Crew, 1977; Dehorn Crew, The; 1 copy; Notes: Liner notes from the legendary vinyl album Solar Sailors Origin: 1977; genreform: Liner notes (Box 8)
    Liner notes; ephemera
  - Some Filk Terms Every Fan Should Know, Strauss, Erwin S.; 1 copy; Notes: This is a crammed sheet of paper with definitions for filk in jokes, like Frank Hayes Disease, Microfilk (also a Filthy Pierre creation), and descriptions of how filk circles are conducted. On the back, crammed together is a directory for microfilk as a PDF that gives an address to access it on Harold's domain, floatingfilk.com/mp3/microfilk.pdf. Origin: Distributed by Filthy Pierre at an east coast filk convention.; genreform: Lexicon (Box 2)
    Lexicon; ephemera
  - Some Filk Terms Every Fan Should Know, Strauss, Erwin S.; 1 copy; Notes: This is a crammed sheet of paper with definitions for filk in jokes, like Frank Hayes Disease, Microfilk (also a Filthy Pierre creation), and descriptions of how filk circles are conducted. On the back, crammed together is a directory for microfilk as a PDF that gives an address to access it on Harold's domain, floatingfilk.com/mp3/microfilk.pdf. Origin: Distributed by Filthy Pierre at an east coast filk convention.; genreform: Lexicon (Box 16)
  - Some Filk Terms Every Fan Should Know, 2006; 1 copy; Notes: Double sided, with A Hundred and One Filk Songs Every Fan Should Know on the back. Origin:; genreform: Handout (Box 14)
  - Songs of Ireland: Brobdignagian Bards, Brobdingnagian Bards; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Brobdignagian Bards Convention: NA; genreform: Poster (Box 7)
  - Sunset's Gold: Music from Anne McCaffrey's HarperHall novels, Oplanad, Tania; Freeman, Mike; 1 copy; Notes: www.opland-freeman.com Origin: NA; genreform: Flier (Box 2)
  - Ten Years of Filk, 1994; 1 copy; Notes: Yellow cover with flying saucer, inscribed on the inside by Glem Simser and Sandi Marie, binder constricter. A list of filk discography from various performers. Origin: Taper Press; genreform: Index (Box 14)
    Index; ephemera
  - Tent card for Harold, 1 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Tent Card (Box 9)
    Tent Card; ephemera
  - The 2 minute Haggadah, 2017; Speigel, Kenny; 1 copy; Notes: Email forward Origin: 2017 Convention: NA; genreform: Haggadah (Box 7)
    Convention -- NA; Haggadah; ephemera
  - The Chieri, sheet music/Dragon Lords, 1979; McQuillin, Cynthia, 1953-2006; Wayne, Phillip; 1 copy; Notes: White, double sided Origin: 1979; genreform: Leaflet (Box 2)
  - The Kitting Out Cheap Handbook, 2016; Korra'ti, Dara; Bohnhoff, Jeff; 2 copy; Notes: Printed out from a workshop at Conflikt 2016 Origin: v.81, January 2016; genreform: Instruction guide (Box 9)
    Instruction guide; ephemera
  - The Smithtown Messenger, 3 January 2019; 1 copy; Notes: Obituary for Harold M. Stein, published in local paper. Written by Phyllis Stein. Origin:; genreform: Newspaper (Box 14)
    Newspaper; ephemera
  - Two laminated bookmarks with botanical themes, 2 copy; Notes: Origin: Possibly bought for/from Interfilk Convention: NA; genreform: Bookmarks (Box 7)
    Convention -- NA; Bookmark; ephemera
  - Two plastic topped coasters with musical designs, 2 copy; Notes: Origin: Possibly Interfilk auction?; genreform: Musical coasters (square) (Box 8)
    Musical coasters (square); ephemera
  - Unidentified man in a peasant shirt and a woman in a corset with a guitar and bass, 1 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Photo (Box 7)
    Photo; ephemera
  - Untitled collection, probably an insert from a recording (includes liner notes for instrumentals), 1993; Torres, Cris; 1 copy; Notes: Song titles include: Into Your World, Cold Heart, Talia, Pins and Needles Origin: Copyright 1993; genreform: Liner notes (Box 8)
  - Why We Still Love Star Wars, 3 December 2017; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: 43072; genreform: Newspaper insert (Box 8)
    Newspaper insert; ephemera
  - Wing Words, Volume 5, #2, 2012; 1 copy; Notes: White, double sided newsletter Origin:; genreform: Newsletter (Box 14)
    Newsletter; ephemera
  - Yesterday's Songs Transformed: A Historical Tour of Song Rewriting, Smashwords edition, 2018; McGath, Gary; Smashwords; 1 copy; Notes: Hardcopy printout of digital file, unbound in a plastic bag with an elastic band Origin: Smashwords, 2018; genreform: Printout of book (Box 11)
    Printout of book; ephemera
- Miscellaneous
  - Greenmantle: A Pagan Journal, 2011; Kimberley, Talis; Beltaine 2011 edition; 1 copy; Notes: With CD that contains Talis Kimberley tracks Origin: Beltaine 2011 edition; genreform: Greenmantle (Box 8)
    Greenmantle
  - Guitar chords, 1 copy; Notes: Origin:; genreform: Guitar chords (Box 9)
    Guitar chords
  - Star Trek: Journey to Babel, 2nd Edition Final Draft, 1967; Desilu Productions, Inc; 1 copy; Notes: Autographed to Lisa Origin: Desilu Productions, Inc. Sept 19, 1967; genreform: Script (Box 11)
    Script
  - A packet of Avery address labels, Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Notes: 25 sheets, Avery #8160 Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: NA; genreform: Address Labels (Box 7)
    Convention -- NA; Address Labels; ephemera
  - A packet of Avery business card blanks, Floating Filk Studios; 2 copy; Notes: 10 sheets, Avery #28371 Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: NA; genreform: Business card blanks (Box 7)
    Convention -- NA; Business card blanks; ephemera
  - A packet of multipurpose labels, Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Notes: 14 sheets, Avery #6467 Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: NA; genreform: Multipurpose Labels (Box 7)
    Convention -- NA; Multipurpose Labels; ephemera